[Music]  oh  [Music]  one of these  [Music]  right here at the baseball game  [Music]  [Music]  [Applause]  foreign  [Music]  is  [Music]  is  [Music]  oh  [Music]  what does it mean to be happy  cause it looks like we all don't know  last half full or empty  man we just putting on a show  we try to look to the heavens  to tell us things that we beg to know  like what did this all mean  if there's no tomorrow  [Music]  what does it mean to be happy  cause it looks like we all don't know  last half full or empty  man we just wouldn't want to shop  we tried to look to the heavens  like what did this all mean  if there's no tomorrow oh yeah  i try to find a  [Music]  to purpose a purpose  oh  [Music]  [Music]  [Music]  you